http://www.glenstreet.com.au/your-theatre/privacy-policy

Jump to navigation Jump to main content Accessibility and Audio Descriptions
Close
You are hereHome /Your Theatre /Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy
Share Share on Facebook
Share this on Twitter
Pin this page on Pinterest
Publish this post to LinkedIn
Glen Street Theatre is committed to observing the national privacy principles as set out in the NSW Privacy and Personal Information Protection Act 1998. Collection of Personal Information When you engage in online activities on this site, Glen Street Theatre may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. These forms are completely optional, but if you wish to engage in activities such as purchasing tickets it is required that where a ‘required’ stated field occurs, it is filled in. Without this information your purchase cannot be processed. Glen Street Theatre may ask that you provide us with personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone and  and other personal identifying information. If you do not provide required data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. How your personal information is usedGlen Street Theatre collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. The information that you provide is used to contact you should an instance occur with relation to online purchasing, performance schedule changes and other unforeseen circumstances. Opt In to Hear From usIf you select to Opt In to receive further information from us, the information provided will also used as part of our effort to keep you informed about upcoming events, and where you have specified, to inform you of special offers via regular email or mail communication. If you Opt In to receive future communications, we may use Your Information, and we may provide Your Information to the promoters and performing companies of those events you attend or book tickets for, enabling the Glen Street Theatre, promoters and performing companies to keep you informed.If the Glen Street Theatre provides Your Information to promoters or performing companies we require these organisations to agree to comply with our Privacy Policy and with strict conditions governing how personal information is to be handled. Financial information will not be shared with any third party.Glen Street Theatre will not otherwise trade, sell or rent personal information about our customers to or with third parties.Alteration of personal informationYou have the right to access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences at any time. You may access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences by writing to Glen Street Theatre at: admin@glenstreet.com.au  What's OnView calendarSubscribeBecome a memberSign up to our newsletterHear about events and special offers as they happen.  Name  Email*  Subscribe
Contact UsSponsorsHow to Find UsLatest NewsJoin the TeamAccess ServicesPrivacy PolicyTheatre FAQsOur HistoryYour Account
NBC Glenstreet MenuWhat's OnTheatreMusicFamilyDanceFilmSpecial EventsCalendarCOVID-19 UpdatesBookSeating PlanGift VouchersCode of PracticeMembershipEducationEducation ShowsBooking InformationPlanning Your TripVenue HireMarketing Opportunities for Venue HirersVenue Booking EnquiryTicketing and Marketing ScheduleYour TheatreContact UsSponsorsHow to Find UsLatest NewsJoin the TeamAccess ServicesPrivacy PolicyTheatre FAQsOur HistoryYour Account
Back to top
Contact Box Office:9975 1455Connect with us on social mediaSocial Media GST Follow Glen Street Theatre on Facebook
Follow Glen Street Theatre on Twitter
Follow Glen Street Theatre on Instagram
Follow Glen Street Theatre on Linkedin
Footer menu bottom - Glen St TheatreContact UsAccessibilityDisclaimerWebsite help
